export let data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Avaveo",
    answers: "Fundamental impactful analyzer",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Blogtag",
    answers: "Centralized intermediate framework",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Cogidoo",
    answers: "Re-engineered analyzing customer loyalty",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Kazu",
    answers: "Synergistic zero defect forecast",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Plajo",
    answers: "Down-sized tertiary leverage",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Zoomzone",
    answers: "De-engineered coherent budgetary management",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "JumpXS",
    answers: "Grass-roots dedicated support",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Dabjam",
    answers: "Inverse executive time-frame",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Thoughtstorm",
    answers: "Adaptive context-sensitive success",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Wikido",
    answers: "Universal incremental conglomeration",
  },
];
